- [laid-back jazz music playing]
- [chattering]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[elevator dings]
[Coop] Back when I was working
at Bailey Russell.
I would start rolling calls
at 7:30 in the morning.
One of the perks of being a thief
was that there was no one to call.
[grunts]
[sighs]
And now. for the first time in my life.
I had more empty hours
than I knew what to do with.
- [woman screaming]
- [chain saw whirs]
You're good.
[tense music playing on screen]
[chewing]
[slurps]
[Coop] It was quiet.
And I had never done well with quiet.
[podcasters chatting]
[podcaster 1] I've never seen Peeping Tom.
- Oh. Ben.
- You'd love it. Ben. You're the Peeper.
[podcaster 2] Let me tell you
- what the basic premise of this movie is.
- [Ben] Please.
[podcaster 2] It's a guy who's obsessed
with the look on people's faces
when they know they're about to die.
He's a cameraman. and he builds a blade
into one of the legs of his tripod.
[Coop] Mel used to complain
that I was never present in my own life.
[podcasters continue]
[sighs]
[Coop] And with all this free time.
I somehow still wasn't.
- [door closes]
- [Barney] You're late.
Sorry.
Is that a Bacon?
It's a print. [sighs]
[massager buzzes]
So. you're processing hundreds
of thousands' worth of merchandise.
How do you convert it?
I have a guy. A fence.
- And you trust him?
- [inhales sharply]
To a point. yeah. [sighs]
It's not like I can
put my business up for bid. [sighs]
- I should meet him.
- Yeah. that's not happening.
I haven't met him either.
if it makes you feel better.
- Thanks. It doesn't.
- [Coop sighs]
Coop. you're light. All right?
You know your net carry has to be
in seven figures to cover your nut.
You're gonna have to be more productive.
Bigger jobs or more of them.
We're disciplined.
We hit 14 houses across the county
over the last year without incident
because we only target things
that won't be missed.
Our whole business plan is based on
people not realizing they were robbed.
- How are you showing income?
- Why do we have to show income?
- Some of us pay taxes.
- I pay taxes!
Don't get bent out of shape. all right?
I'm trying to help you.
- I didn't ask for your help.
- Doesn't mean you don't need it.
Where are you parking your money?
I have small accounts
at a few different banks.
Oh. good. So. there's a paper trail?
Is he always like this?
No. Sometimes he overreacts.
Look. Coop. just…
just humor me. all right?
So. just tell me. what was the plan
for when big ticket items come up. hmm?
You can't pay Princeton
with a brown bag of cash.
Come on. Coop. You know all this.
What did you think you were gonna do?
It was only supposed to be
a stopgap measure.
So. what happened?
Turns out. we're good at it.
[chuckles] Not from where I'm standing.
Fuck you! Why is he even here?
- Why am I here?
- Yeah.
I'm here for him. all right?
Because I was keeping him out of trouble
long before you ever came along.
- [scoffs]
- We're gonna have to wash the money.
Oh. you're gonna wash it?
That means make it seem
like it comes from legitimate sources.
Yeah. I know what money laundering is.
I'm just shocked that a tight-ass suit
like you knows how to do it.
You know. I liked you a lot better
when you were just
Nick's inappropriately hot housekeeper.
Hey!
Coop…
you remember Brett Sutter
from my PwC days?
Didn't he get fired?
Well. he left to work with less.
uh. palatable clients. right?
The kind that primarily deal
in untraceable funds.
I'm pretty sure he can set us up.
Now. we convert the cash into crypto.
tumble it between wallets
and generate fake invoices
to create evidence
of a legitimate revenue stream.
Congratulations.
I'm your business manager again.
What's his end?
I don't know. My guess. 20%.
Twenty percent? Fuck that. [chuckles]
That's off the gross.
Listen. if you guys wanna trust
some scumbag with your money. that's fine.
- [Barney sighs]
- He's not coming anywhere near mine.
Well. she's a bright ray
of sunshine. isn't she?
Barney. what are you doing?
What are you talking about?
You shouldn't be getting involved in this.
You were my biggest client.
Are you looking to get back
into legitimate business anytime soon?
No.
Then I'm getting involved.
I'll set the meeting.
[sighs heavily]
[groans]
[buzzing]
[theme song playing]
♪ A paper shadow in a house of stone ♪
♪ The wooden flag
Of a drifting dreamboat ♪
♪ I never knew
How far the ride was gonna go ♪
♪ Till I looked back at the smoke ♪
♪ You can't keep up with the Joneses ♪
♪ Don't wanna run for the roses ♪
♪ I got my pocket of posies ♪
♪ Sometimes I wonder why ♪
♪ I just don't run with the Joneses ♪
♪ Don't wanna smell the dying roses ♪
♪ I got my pocket full of posies ♪
♪ I don't keep up with the Joneses ♪
[breathing heavily]
[blowing]
[alarm ringing]
[groans. exhales sharply]
[breathes heavily]
[blows]
[sighs]
Uh. hello?
- We're going to be late.
- Good morning.
No. you're not. You're never late.
Hey. are you gonna. um.
check your admissions portal today?
- Why?
- What do you mean. "why"?
You're supposed to hear from Princeton
any day now.
Okay. Mom.
Don't "Okay. Mom" me.
- All right. I see what you did there.
- Did you?
[chuckling] Irony is your love language.
And I love you too.
And then. depression set in.
[pensive music playing]
[coffee machine whirs]
[dance music playing on TV]
[music continues]
[doorbell rings]
[pensive music playing]
- [squelching]
- [gasps. groans]
[exhales sharply]
[sighs]
Fuck.
No. no. You don't wanna see that.
It's split-level and dated.
[knocks on door]
Holly. can you give me a second?
Esperanza. can you get that?
We're in the bath. Miss Samantha!
[sighs]
Well. I went to a…
a dinner party there two years ago.
and the space felt really great
and big and open.
Okay. Great.
I will see you there tomorrow.
9:30. Right. Text me your coffee order.
- All right. Bye.
- New business?
- Yeah.
- Hell yeah.
- Thanks for that. And for this.
- Mmm.
Hey. it's just my way
of saying "Thank you."
[chuckles] It's a pretty big bouquet.
It's a pretty big house.
Owen. you're very charming…
And humble. Right?
But I'm not going to date you.
Wow. Usually people wait for me
to ask them out before they turn me down.
Look. I could see how I might seem to you
like someone who has
their life together and. I mean…
- No. [chuckles] Not really.
- Oh.
I mean. everything you've been through.
I'm sure you're a hot mess.
- Well. that's a fair assessment.
- And it's very sexy.
So you just figured I was vulnerable.
and lonely. and horny.
and desperate to please?
No. that's me.
[both chuckle]
No. I figured you'd have
no patience for bullshit.
And you'd be open and honest with me.
the way no one else around here is.
Well. I appreciate that.
And in that spirit.
I'd just like to reiterate
- that I am not going to date--
- And you're so hot.
- [chuckles]
- It's crazy. really. We can't deny that.
Thank you. But sadly.
I am a committed spinster now.
- I get it. really I do. I do.
- Mm-hmm.
Now. just give me a minute
'cause I'm gonna tell you
all the reasons why
that's a terrible idea.
- Okay. [chuckles]
- Terrible idea.
- Good night.
- Thirty seconds.
Good night. Owen.
It's Ashe.
[chattering]
- [pop music plays on headphones]
- You know that girl?
Started at Mayfield last week.
Her dad is the superrich guy who threw
the thing Mom and Dad went to.
Hmm.
Is she your year?
[Hunter] Yeah.
Well. go talk to her.
Why?
Because she's alone
and it's what people do.
She looks busy.
Hey! New girl!
This is Hunter.
Do you wanna talk to him?
You're welcome.
Hunter Cooper. right?
I think we have bio together.
I'm Delilah Ashe.
Your sister is a lot. huh?
She's also kind of a know-it-all.
And surprisingly messy.
There's like. hair. everywhere.
All the time.
W-What are you drawing?
You.
- That's really good.
- [chuckles] Thanks.
Where were you before this?
Schloss Krumbach.
It's a boarding school in Austria.
Why Austria?
No idea. You'd have to ask my father.
And I'm the last person
who's gonna cape for Austria.
Shitty food and German is
an impossible language.
[chuckles] So why'd you move here?
As far as I can tell.
my father's decided to try his hand
at actually being a parent.
And I guess step one is.
like. completely uprooting
and disrupting your daughter's life.
- And your mom?
- She died when I was eight.
I'm sorry.
Yeah. the dead mother is
kind of a conversation killer.
[stammers] Are you here alone?
No. All my new friends
should be getting here any second.
[both chuckle]
[inhales deeply]
So are you gonna sit down. or what?
Hey.
What are you doing?
- We have a court in ten minutes.
- [sighs]
You have your racket?
Maybe put on some clothes?
Come on. Dad.
Princeton has already made its decision.
Okay. one more session
isn't gonna make a difference.
I'm not worried about Princeton.
I'm worried about me.
All right. you're gonna go away to college
and I'm gonna lose my tennis buddy.
Come on. Let's… [clicks teeth]
Do not start acting like Mom.
She starts to cry
every time she looks at me now.
Well. that's just abject disappointment.
Fair.
Can't we just stay here
and do this instead?
And by this you mean nothing?
Exactly. But with intention.
[hopeful music plays]
[sighs. blows]
[sighs] I think I'm still hungover
from Ashe's party.
- Is that possible?
- [friends chuckle]
Of course it is. We're old as fuck.
My liver definitely is.
Mm-mmm. shut your pretty young mouth.
- Let us hags speak.
- [Suzanne chuckles]
Excuse you. but I am
the mother of an almost five-year-old.
Oh. sorry in advance for
the birthday party tomorrow. guys.
It is gonna be as tacky as they come.
- [Julie chuckles]
- That's on me.
You can take the girl
out of Long Island. but…
[others coo. laugh]
J-Just keep the pool covered so
Diane doesn't decide to take another swim.
- [friends laugh]
- Okay.
I know I should be mortified. all right.
But I don't remember anything
that happened after meeting Mr. Ashe. so…
But him you remember.
- He does make quite an impression.
- [Diane sighs]
- Mmm.
- Really?
Yeah. I'm gay. not blind.
[all chuckle]
You know. Mel. he is single.
No. thank you.
[friend] Oh. come on. Mel.
It's been ages since you and Nick split.
Ashe is fresh meat.
No local baggage.
- [chuckles] He's not my type.
- Mmm.
- Bullshit. He's everybody's type.
- [chuckling]
Come on. Mel.
Get you some horizontal refreshment.
[all laughing]
You know with Tori off to college.
you are one kid away from an empty nest.
We're not telling you to marry him.
just have some fun.
Yeah. like that worked out
so well the last time.
No one told you
to move Nick into your house.
You can't just put your vag
on a shelf. Mel.
- [chuckles]
- [Diane] What?
At our age.
it's a use it or lose it proposition.
- [mutters]
- I am exclusively focused on my book.
I am like a monk.
You know those monks fuck each other.
- [chuckling]
- What?
It's the robes. Easy access.
[chuckling]
Is it weird that thinking about that
is making me hungry?
- [chuckling] Yes.
- I love you.
The buffet beckons.
[groans]
Oh. geez.
Everything okay?
[Mel] Mmm.
No.
I went on a date this last week
and my lady bits…
I don't know how to talk about this.
They… I think it's normal. but…
Oh. you bitch.
You're just starting perimenopause?
I think so. right?
'Cause I can't sleep.
I'm sweating constantly.
like. just drenched.
You're glowing.
I-I can't focus on my writing.
which could just be
'cause I suck at writing.
But… [stammers]
Help?
Do hormone replacement therapy.
[sucks teeth] Just like that?
No. it's totally safe.
- I don't know.
- [scoffs]
You might feel differently when you
start punching random people in the face.
W-What do you mean?
It happens.
You will feel the urge to murder people.
I tried to strangle my brother
at a barbecue.
- Why?
- No reason.
It's a personal choice.
So. either take hormones
or count myself out sexually
from here until forever?
No. of course not.
There's so many more people
I would've had sex with.
You could do the MonaLisa Touch.
The Mona… [mumbles] …what?
It's a laser treatment
to prevent vaginal atrophy.
[laughs]
- Oh.
- Yeah.
[stammers] Vaginal…
Yeah. helps with the dryness.
It promotes collagen growth.
It's expensive. but you can
happily fuck your way into your 70s.
It just requires more maintenance.
Call my guy. I'm telling you.
Vaginal…
- Atrophy.
- …atrophy?
Oh. [chuckles]
He'll fix you right up.
Is that a medical term?
[person] Hello. Yeah. Yeah. That's right.
Great to meet you.
Syrup on eggs?
Don't food-shame me.
You told me
to lay off pancakes altogether.
Well. that's not food-shaming.
It's fat-shaming.
Oh. That's okay. then. huh?
- Oh. come on. Such a stellar role model.
- [child giggles]
- Mmm. So good.
- Oh. you think that's funny?
- You're gonna stuff pancakes in too?
- [muffled] Hi. Mel.
- [Mel] Hey.
- Jesus.
Where were you?
I could've used some backup in the sauna.
Oh. I just got my annual keratin.
So. two days before I can get my hair wet.
- Why. what'd I miss?
- [sighs]
They were trying to pimp me out.
Pimp… To whom?
- It's great to meet you.
- Thank you. Glad you had a good time.
Yeah. we'll see you soon. I'm sure.
Yes. Yes. you should totally do that.
And by that. I mean him.
- And by do. I mean fuck him so hard…
- [stammering]
…until. like. things start to hurt.
- I get it.
- Please. you know. for the rest of us.
[Mel] I get it. Yep.
Your family is still eating.
[classical music playing]
This whole gratuitously lavish buffet.
and you're going for wheat toast.
Want some cornflakes with that? [chuckles]
- I'm a simple man.
- [chuckles]
Uh. I think both of us know
that's not true.
Yeah? How do you mean?
Well. I mean. even if I wasn't good
at reading people.
which I am by the way.
you. my friend.
have complicated written all over you.
[chuckles] Well. as you already found out.
uh. life didn't exactly work out
the way it was planned.
Hey. I can relate. man.
Yeah. you seem
pretty complicated yourself.
Oh. you have no idea.
- I bet.
- [chuckles]
Well. the party was a hit.
Everybody's talking about it.
It was good. right? It was fun.
- I can go a little overboard sometimes.
- [chuckling] You think?
My therapist told me
I have no concept of boundaries.
[chuckles] Of course.
I was sleeping with her at the time.
- Ah. As one does.
- Yeah.
But. as far as I can tell.
you and I have a lot in common.
Including being the only single men
in town who aren't NBA All-Stars.
I was hoping you could point me
in the right direction.
- Uh…
- Know what I mean?
Yeah. well. I'm afraid it's. uh.
pretty slim pickings
around here at Westmont Village.
It's pretty much a married crowd.
Oh. [sighs] Shit. yeah.
I don't love dating married women.
I mean. the sex is great.
They seem like they have a lot to prove.
but then you gotta listen to them
moaning about their shitty husbands
while you try to sleep.
And all of a sudden. they've turned
a hot fling into another shitty marriage.
- [toast pops up]
- [chuckles] Toast.
Sounds like you have some experience
in this arena.
I've been single longer than you.
And I'm a widower.
Women love a sad man.
Yeah. sad is not the vibe I get from you.
We should go out in the city sometime.
you and me.
It'd be great. I'm a great wingman.
I'm not saying you need it.
You don't need it.
You got the whole suburban
James Bond thing working.
It's good.
I bet you get laid all the time.
don't you?
- [chuckles]
- I do too.
But it's more because
I throw money around.
Not in a sex worker kind of way.
Although if that's your thing.
then. yeah. no judgment here.
[laughs. sighs]
I'm gonna get back to my kids.
I'll come with you.
- Mmm.
- Okay.
Nice job on the toast.
Thanks.
You and Ashe look awfully buddy-buddy.
[slurps]
Yeah. he's a real one. [chuckles]
You know.
he's got a lot of ideas for the gym.
Sounds like he may want to get involved.
If we do these next two locations right.
we won't have to take on
any outside investment.
You can retain complete ownership.
Yeah. that's true.
And the way these endorsements
are rolling in…
Hey. would you buy deodorant from me?
I would seriously…
- consider it.
- You would?
[mysterious music playing]
[Coop] So. how well do you know this guy?
Better than you know Nick's housekeeper.
- Elena.
- I know her name.
Seriously. what were you thinking?
She had a gun on me.
Oh. she carries a gun.
Great.
Oh!
- Hey. [chuckles]
- Hey. Get over here. Choi.
- Good to see you.
- How's the wife?
- The kids? All good?
- All good.
Hey. How's Denise?
[scoffs] Long gone. my friend.
She absconded to Florida
with her personal trainer.
- Oh. I'm sorry to hear that. man.
- Yeah. Thank God for prenups. right?
- [both chuckle]
- Brett Sutter.
Hey. Andrew Cooper.
You look a lot better than your mug shot.
- I would hope so.
- I don't mean anything by it.
I couldn't pretend
I didn't know who you were.
Well. Coop was acquitted.
Doesn't matter to me.
- Find me a client without a body. right?
- Mmm.
Hey. thanks for coming by. fellas.
I find these conversations are better had
in a controlled environment.
- Come on. Sit down.
- [Coop clears throat]
So… [sighs] …Coop. Barney tells me
you need the fluff and fold treatment.
Well… [stammers]
I'm not sure exactly what I need.
Coop's come into an unexpected windfall.
You know. we can't source it completely.
but need it for legitimate expenses.
And this unexpected. unsourceable money
we imagine it's gonna keep coming?
Yeah.
All right. [sniffs] Here's how I'd do it.
Barney. you're the courier.
Now. you deposit the funds
in my crypto exchange
on behalf of some dummy finance company.
I use a proven series of hops.
mixers and bridges
to obscure the origin of the money.
Eventually. you invoice me
from an LLC you set up.
Invoice you for what?
Well. you're consulting for me.
Well. not me.
For one or two companies I own. [sighs]
And I remit taxable payments
to your company.
Minus my commission.
- And how much is that?
- Thirty.
Bullshit. Twenty.
Thirty is industry-standard.
Oh. [stammers] I must've missed that
in the newsletter.
[scoffs] I'll do it for a quarter.
[inhales deeply] Deal.
What's the lead time on this?
After we set up your dummy wallets…
- [fingers snap]
- …like that.
I'm gonna get you boys some whiskeys.
We can get into the. uh. dirty details.
all right?
[mysterious music playing]
I'll come up with something else.
[Samantha] It's no problem. Marcia.
[Marcia. on phone]
I don't wanna be difficult. but…
Please. you're not being difficult.
You mean. you want what you want.
I mean. I love the house.
but. at this price point.
I just need to be reassured
that we're not gonna be limited
by zoning restrictions
once we start renovating.
How do we get clarity on that?
You know what? Let me do some digging
on my end and I'll get back to you soon.
- Okay. great. That'd be wonderful.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Yep. Okay. bye.
Bye.
[pony blusters]
[sighs]
- Fuck it.
- [tires screech]
[playful music playing]
[partygoers chattering]
I mean. he didn't even…
Oh. my God.
[wistful music playing]
- Did you know she was coming?
- I sure didn't.
I definitely didn't ask.
- Babe. don't.
- Just give me a second.
[Maggie] Sam. wait.
Sam!
Was Henry the only kid in class
who wasn't invited?
It wasn't meant to be such a big thing.
It just… It kind of blew up.
He just lost his father. Maggie.
- Do you have even an ounce of compassion?
- Of course I do.
Look. it's a complicated situation.
There are a lot of raw feelings.
Oh. my God. He is a five-year-old boy.
No one would've cared if he was here.
It wasn't Henry we were worried about.
I could've sent him with someone else.
What was I supposed to do?
Invite him and not you?
Yes!
Because that would've
only been moderately shitty of you.
Instead. you decide
to exclude a five-year-old boy
who's still reeling
from his father's suicide.
- Sam--
- He thinks Daisy is his best friend.
I don't think you appreciate
the position you've put us all in.
This is because of Mel.
That's not what I said.
Jesus Christ. it feels like
I'm in high school all over again.
Did you frame someone for murder
in high school?
Fuck you. Maggie.
And you can tell yourself
all the lies you want.
but there's no version of this
where you didn't just take a cheap shot
at a little boy.
He didn't do anything to anyone.
I know.
- I wish it didn't have to be this way.
- That's the thing. Maggie.
It doesn't.
[pensive music playing]
[metal jingling]
[dog panting. groaning]
[playfully suspenseful music playing]
- Hey. buddy.
- [barking]
[gasps]
[barking continues]
All right.
Easy. Hi.
Hey. buddy. Are you friendly?
Are you friend…
Hey! Hey!
Go shit in your own yard!
Shoo!
Get the fuck outta here.
Fucking dumbass.
Yeah. you better run.
- Mel. Hi.
- Hi. Brienne.
This is a surprise.
Hey. did you just work out or something?
No.
W-Well. you just have
a little. um. moisture.
- Oh.
- Moisture right there.
- Yeah. yeah. yeah. right there.
- Uh. just walked all the way over.
- [chuckles]
- Okay.
Hi. Is… Is everything okay?
Um. yeah. Ish. Um…
[clicks tongue]
Did you and Clay happen to just buy a dog?
Arlo.
Yes. We didn't buy him.
We rescued him.
He was sent back twice.
and then given to a kill shelter.
I mean. can you believe that?
Oh. Yes.
- Uh. no.
- [sighs]
- The thing is. your dog…
- Arlo.
- Arlo is using my backyard as a toilet.
- Yeah.
Oh. Really?
[chuckles] Well. I'm sorry about that.
I'm thrilled that he's found
his forever home.
but if you could just make sure
he stays in his forever yard…
We will definitely try.
The thing with mastiffs is
that they tend to wander.
and they kind of prefer to. like.
roam free. you know?
In the English countryside
in the 19th century.
but we're in Westchester now.
Yeah. I will. um. do my best.
[chuckles]
Thank you.
Thanks for coming by!
[melancholy music playing]
[chuckles]
[school bell rings]
["Your One Way Street"
playing on headphones]
♪ Feeling something's leaving ♪
♪ But I can't change what's happening ♪
[music stops]
Hey. [chuckles]
You look different.
[sighs] No shit.
[chuckles] I'm also itchy
and lightly nauseous.
I don't know why. [sighs]
It's just some… [stammers]
…stuffy elitist prep school.
[chuckles] No offense.
- They're gonna judge me.
- No. You'll be great.
You think so?
[stammers] Not at the interview part.
- But at the teaching. yeah.
- [chuckles] Okay.
- Hey. Hunter.
- Hey.
Wassup?
Delilah. this is my aunt. Ali.
The singer?
[gasps] You talked about me? Aw.
It's nice to meet you.
You too.
- [Ali] Delilah. [chuckles]
- [Delilah chuckles]
Cool.
Well. I am just gonna go stand over there
and sweat my balls off.
[Ali. Delilah chuckle]
Is she okay?
[stammers] Unclear.
So this is a lot.
but my dad got me insane floor seats
to see The Walkmen at the Beacon tonight.
You're kidding. I love The Walkmen.
He's feeling guilty for all the moving
around. so he's trying to buy me friends.
[inhales sharply]
So I guess my question for you is.
are you for sale?
Oh. yeah. You had me at floor seats.
Great. We'll pick you up at 5:00.
Give me your info.
Hey. Hunter.
Hey.
Hi. I'm Morgan.
Are you new here?
Yes. I'm Delilah.
I just transferred in.
With three months left of school?
I like to up the degree of difficulty
wherever I can.
I love your boots.
Thanks.
Ms. Cooper?
Dr. Seelbach is ready for you.
[Ali] Okay.
Hunter?
Hey. um. do I have anything in my teeth?
- [Hunter] All clear.
- [Ali] Are you sure?
- 'Cause I had kale salad for lunch…
- Bye.
…with a little tuna. Um. how's my breath?
[exhales deeply]
Good luck in there.
Good luck out here.
[door opens. closes]
[school bell rings]
["Messy" playing on radio]
♪ And then I'm too fucking clean ♪
♪ You told me. "Get a job"
Then you ask where the hell I've been ♪
♪ And I'm too perfect ♪
♪ Till I open my big mouth ♪
♪ I want to be me ♪
♪ Is that not allowed? ♪
- ♪ And I'm too clever ♪
- [song stops]
- Surprise!
- [cheering. laughing]
- [Coop exclaims]
- [Mel] You got in.
- I never doubted you for a second.
- [Ron] Way to go. honey.
- [laughs] Cupcakes.
- Baby. have a cupcake.
- [laughing]
- Wait. how…
How could you know that I got in?
I checked your Common app.
You left your password on our iCloud.
You had no right to do that.
Hey. she just wanted to get ahead of it
so we could surprise you.
Why don't you seem excited?
Well. she's probably in shock.
[chuckles] I mean. look at this fuss.
Hey. what's going on?
[sighs] I was gonna talk
to you guys about this.
About what?
[sighs]
I'm not going to Princeton.
[breathes shakily]
I already declined.
[sighs]
[singsongy] Surprise.
- [Mel] Tori.
- Whoa. whoa. Mel.
[Mel] No.
Baby. talk to us.
- What's going on?
- I told you. I declined the offer.
What do you mean you declined the offer?
That's not funny.
Do you see me laughing?
If you were… [stammers] …having doubts.
why didn't you tell us?
Because I knew it would
pretty much go like this.
- Tori Cooper. you--
- Okay. Hey. [stammers] Hey.
Hey. Let's calm down. please.
- Did you know about this?
- Of course I didn't know about this.
- What…
- What is happening here?
- Did something happen?
- No.
- What-What are you not telling us?
- Nothing. Mom.
You're just not accepting
what I am telling you.
Of course I'm not accepting it.
You just spent the last four years
working your ass off to get in.
Now. suddenly overnight
you decide you don't wanna go?
Is there another college
- that you wanted to choose?
- What?
No. I don't know if
I wanna go to college at all.
[chuckling] Okay.
I'm-I'm not following.
Do you have any idea
what she's talking about?
I'm making my way up to it.
Yes. I'm trying to figure it out.
Tori. do you think you might be more
comfortable talking about it with me?
- Mom.
- I'm just trying to help.
No. thank you. We've got it.
It doesn't look that way to me.
- Okay. thanks.
- Wow.
Guys. let's all push pause. huh?
I-I-I get that you clearly have
a lot on your mind right now.
Maybe you could've shared some of this
information with us a little bit earlier.
But why don't we three go somewhere
and sit down and try to figure out
what's going on?
Nothing's going on.
I'm just… [sighs]
I'm not sure that I want the same things
that you guys want for me.
Tori. [stammers] Us wanting you to go
to college isn't some outrageous thing.
It's college.
Everything has always been
about what you guys want.
You've never once bothered
to ask me if it's what I wanted.
Okay. [stammers] Okay.
Uh. I'm sorry. all right?
This is… This is us asking.
what-what do… what do you want?
I don't know.
- [sighs]
- Oh. my God.
[quietly] Are you pregnant?
Fuck. Mom!
Hey. I…
- I'm talking to you.
- Pregnant? Are you fucking serious?
I'm sorry. It just came out.
- Can you wait a minute? Hey.
- Stop. Mom.
- [Mel screams] Oh. my God. Tori!
- [screams]
- [Coop] Jesus Christ.
- Oh. my goodness. Sweetie.
- Jesus! Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
- Did you hit your head?
- It's fine. I'm fine.
- Yeah.
- [Mel] So sorry. sweetheart.
Okay. can we just talk about
something else. please?
[breathes heavily]
[Coop sighs]
Hey. uh…
I'm gonna be teaching at Mayfield now.
[Hunter] You got the job?
Yeah. They hired me on the spot.
I would've told you all sooner.
but I didn't wanna step on Tori's thing.
and since it's no longer a thing. uh…
Surprise. [chuckles]
I thought we talked about this.
- [quietly] We did and I told her--
- What is that now?
- Nothing. It's…
- Nothing.
He was worried it might be
too much for you. I disagreed.
Ah.
Hey. Andy. quick question.
- What the fuck?
- Okay. You know what?
Thanks for that. Thank you.
All right.
so you're trying to control Ali too.
Does anyone ever age out. or is it
just your plan to control us all forever?
Tori. I just wanna say
this is the same age that Ali was
when she started to rebel.
and look what happened to her.
- Mom. Mom. Not…
- There it is.
- Not a great time for this.
- Don't pay any attention to her.
- We're very proud of you.
- I'm just trying to help.
- Yeah. maybe try a little less. dear.
- [groans]
You just can't handle the fact that
I'm not following the exact path you did.
Sweetheart. college is where you go
to find your path.
Right. okay. And how has
that worked out for you and Dad?
What? Because we…
Because our marriage didn't work out?
- Is that what this is about?
- No. your lives didn't work out.
Okay. you lost your job.
You both did.
And now. you're starting over
and Mom thinks she's gonna write a book.
Okay. Tori. cool it. all right?
[sighs]
Okay. So. what is your grand plan?
I don't have a plan yet.
You're not giving me any room
to breathe or figure it out.
I need some air.
- Baby. I--
- [Tori] Don't follow me.
[sighs]
[pensive music plays]
Hey.
She's doing this to punish us.
It might not be about us.
Of course it's about us.
Look at the last year she's had.
This is a classic trauma response
to the whole mess you got us into.
[scoffs] Really?
I'm sorry.
I'm just… just spinning out here.
Maybe there is something to
what Tori is actually saying.
- You're on her side?
- I'm not on anyone's side.
I'm not taking sides.
I'm just saying. let's hear her out.
This is not the time to
treat her like a rational actor.
She's being reckless and rebellious
and she's gonna blow up her whole life.
Maybe. And maybe we have to let her.
Don't do that.
This isn't Ali.
You can't tell me not to parent
my own daughter. our daughter.
[muffled music playing]
You have the wrong driveway.
They're here for me.
- What do you mean?
- Just going to a concert with Delilah.
Wha… [stammers] Excuse me. with who?
Hey. hey.
Oh.
[chuckles]
Hey. Delilah. say hi.
Coop. Melanie. Great to see ya.
I'll have him home by midnight. maybe.
- Hey.
Sorry about that and this
and everything to come.
Trust me. it's way better than
what's going on in my house.
Hey. Hunter! You ready to rock?
Dad. please take it down several notches.
What was that? Sorry. I can't hear you.
You're like a mile away.
[laughs] Maybe just call me.
I don't trust that guy.
Certainly is friendly.
Where are you going?
To find her and get to the bottom of this.
Just give her some space. huh?
[chuckles] I know you mean well.
but getting parenting advice from you
is really hard right now.
Yeah. and your way is working really well.
If you wanna be helpful.
go in there and get rid of your family.
I'm just… Not you. Ron.
Course not.
[exhales]
Hey. Dad. [sighs]
Sorry you had to witness that.
That?
That was nothing.
It's hard when you reach the point where
you can't protect your kids
the way you used to.
Not from the world.
not from their own choices.
I'm her father.
If I can't protect her. then who?
Well. it's not that you can't.
It's that she won't let you.
[sighs]
Because you've raised a smart
and fiercely independent daughter.
Which doesn't mean she is not gonna
screw up. She will. a lot.
And that's when being a father
becomes really tricky.
because it's no longer about
telling her what to do.
[sighs]
It's about finding a way to let go
while still keeping everyone close.
She's making choices that
are gonna wreck her life.
That's the hardest part
because your job is no longer to stop her.
Your job is to stay on the sidelines.
Just make sure she knows
you're there for her
when she realizes she needs you.
[exhales]
Well. I'm glad you're here.
- Thanks.
- [grunts]
- You coming? [sighs]
- Give me five more minutes.
I could use a break from your mother.
Jesus. Take ten.
[chuckles. sniffles]
[Coop sighs]
[squelching]
[gasps. screams]
Fuck you! [panting]
Not you.
[Coop] I was dealing with an aching back
and a familial clusterfuck.
So. I wasn't really in the mood to work.
but this job didn't come with sick days
or paid family leave.
And the fact was.
I knew Ashe and his daughter
were out for the night
and that he hadn't staffed up yet.
So. there was a window we couldn't ignore.
I also knew his house had a lot of doors.
and he didn't seem like
the kind of guy who would do a circuit
to make sure they were all locked.
[clicks]
Okay. I got a door.
You're absolutely positive
there's no security system installed yet?
He is taking bids from Héctor's company
and two others next week.
[Coop] Staff?
I already told you
he hired Hennah's cousin.
and she starts tomorrow.
You're being quiet.
It's been a long night.
- You wanna talk about it?
- Not particularly.
Good. Let's talk about Barney then.
What about him?
I just… I don't understand why
you wanna bring more people into this.
[Coop] Because he's right.
If we keep working at this clip.
we're gonna need to find some way
to make all this money
we're earning look legit.
Otherwise. we're gonna be sitting
on piles of cash that we can't use.
Well. where I live. cash is still king.
We might not need Barney yet.
but there's only so much money
you can stuff under a mattress.
[chuckles] I don't know. Coop.
It sounds to me like
you're still trying to have it both ways.
What is that supposed to mean?
You're a thief and you want a 401(k).
I think you need to decide who you are
and be that person.
I contain multitudes.
Multitudes of bullshit.
All right. Elena. look.
Barney is consulting for us like Héctor.
And you're my only partner.
Fine.
Maybe it is time that I got
the white guy treatment.
like you and Barney.
Okay. You know. Barney is not white.
Mmm. Does he know that?
[Coop] Edith Wharton's The House of Mirth.
Signed. first edition. first printing.
American issue
with frontispiece
and seven illustrated plates.
Pristine condition. with an estimated
value of up to $115.000 at auction.
And it's not even her masterpiece.
that would be The Age of Innocence.
That one that made her the first woman
to win a Pulitzer Prize for fiction.
Well. she technically only won
after the jury's original selection.
Sinclair Lewis's Main Street.
was disqualified.
Not that it mattered
to collectors like Ashe.
Who had almost certainly
never even cracked the spine.
These books were purchased by the yard.
probably by a book stylist.
Just another way to dress his walls
with appreciating assets.
- [Elena] Coop.
- Yeah. Yeah. I got it.
I'm coming out.
All right.
You're showing some healthy gains.
but you need to diversify
a little bit more.
And for God's sake.
stop investing in T-bills.
You're just leaving money on the table.
- You get that SEP IRA set up yet?
- [door slams]
Talk to her.
You need the shelter.
[door buzzes]
Quit rabble-rousing. Coop.
What do you have for me today?
Hmm.
Edith Wharton.
First edition.
Excellent condition.
Well. I can move this.
I always preferred Jane Austen myself.
[inhales sharply]
I would not have called that.
We were all young once.
What about you?
I'm more of a movie guy.
Ugh. that's what's wrong
with your generation.
No appreciation for the finer arts.
Speaking of. did you find a buyer
for the Bacon yet?
Still too hot. [chuckles]
The owner has done everything
short of alerting Interpol
that it was stolen.
You're gonna have to sit on it
for a while.
Maybe even another year.
What if I don't have another year?
- [phone ringing]
- Then you'll probably end up in prison.
[exhales deeply]
Hey. Barney.
I'm right in the middle of something.
Can I call you back in like ten?
[Barney]
Okay. but actually call me back for once.
I may have found a solution
to our little logistics problem.
Sorry about that. [sighs]
Always be closing. right?
[chuckles] Mamet. Nice.
Thank you for this.
I have to get back to work.
[stammers] Sidney.
Later. Frank.
[J.J.] Harvey. I often wish I were deaf
and wore a hearing aid.
With a simple flick of a switch.
I could shut out
the greedy murmur of little men.
[Sidney]
J.J.. I need your ear for two minutes.
- [J.J.] Mac!
- [Mac] Yes?
[J.J.] I don't want this man at my table…
[Sidney]
I've got a message from your sister.
- [humming]
- [whirring]
Hey. Coop.
Ashe. what are you doing here?
Hey. did Hunter have a good time
at the show?
He's a really. really nice kid.
Little quiet. but polite.
And I think my daughter may have
a little crush on him. [chuckles]
[chuckles]
Is there something I can help you with?
I don't mean to be rude.
but I got a bunch of calls and…
Yeah.
Remember when I told you
you're a complicated guy?
Yeah.
Well. it turns out.
I had no idea how complicated.
[exhales deeply]
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-